

## **PROFILE**

20 year's experience as Linux system administrator, DevOps, ICT Manager and Network Administrator.
Skilled with Linux OS, CentOS and Ubuntu.

Good experience with SQL and NoSQL, ProxySQL, Nginx, HAProxy. Skilled with Docker, Docker Swarm, Kubernetes, VMware vSphere 7 ESXI, OWASP.

Skilled on Network Switching, Routing and Security.

Experience with AWS services Route 53, EC2, Lambda, S3, CloudWatch, IAM

Programming Language with PHP, Python, JavaScript's, MVC. Skilled on ELK, LEMP, MERN STACK Skilled with ERP systems like SAP, Skilled on CI/CD tools like Ansible, Puppet, .

## CONTACT

PHONE: +989127789404

WEBSITE:

https://alidev.pro

**EMAIL:** 

Ali.yousefzadeh@gmail.com

LinkedIn:

https://bit.ly/3fuPnn6

#### **HOBBIES**

Hiking Literature Swimming

# **ALI YOUSEFZADEH**

Team Lead, DevOps, Sysadmin

## **EDUCATION**

## Apply Mathematics in Computer at Tehran Polytechnic University

1994 - 1998

Main Course I loved was: Statistical, Advanced Programming, Computational Theory, Abstract Algebra, Differential Equations

## **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## EasyMarkets - Linux System Admin (Limassol – Cyprus)

Jun 2021- Now

Forex Company

Tools: Ansible, Nginx, MySQL, MongoDB, Memcached, GitHub Action

# Free Lancer - Technical Product Manager and DevOps ( Tehran – Iran )

Jul 2019-May 2021

Mahan VolP Co: Auto Call Dialer, Call Center System

HoshmandRisk Co: Mutual fund, Brokerage, Portfolio, Risk Management

Varlee Co: Stores and wallets Management system

Evand Co: Information system, ticket sales and online registration of events, webinars, conferences and seminars

Tools: Redis, Elastic Search, GITLAB CI/CD, Docker Compose, Docker file, Zabbix, Jenkins, performance testing and reporting tools.

## Nesko Inc. – DevOps (Toronto – Canada)

Sep 2018-Jul 2019

transportation ecosystem that connects passenger to a network of taxi companies for Canadian company in south of America.

Tools: AWS EC2, Ansible, AWS Elastic cash, VPC, Route 53, S3, Lambda

## Carpino and Carboy Co - Team lead (Tehran – Iran )

Jun 2016-Sep 2018

Carpino is Intelligent taxi system

Carboy is Intelligent on-site car service system

Tools: Mongodb, Postgres, MySQL, MQTT, Jenkins, Zabbix. Pentaho. Jira.

#### TANA Co - PM and Sysadmin (Tehran – Iran )

Jul 2013-Jun 2016

Tehran UNICEF App, website for UNHabitat, Kids Learning app, ...

## Stratus Co - ICT Manager (Tehran – Iran )

Sep 2007- Jul 2013

International Construction company with a huge computer's network and SAP ERP System, Panasonic VolP,...

